adforum.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Info

Your privacy is critically important to us. At AdForum we have a few fundamental principles:

AdForum LLC ( **AdForum** ) operates AdForum.com. It is AdForum’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

Like most website operators, AdForum collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. AdForum’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how AdForum’s visitors use its website. From time to time, AdForum may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

AdForum also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. AdForum does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

Certain visitors to AdForums websites choose to interact with AdForum in ways that require AdForum to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that AdForum gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up account at AdForum.com to provide a username and email address. AdForum collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with AdForum. AdForum does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

AdForum may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. AdForum may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, AdForum does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

AdForum discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AdForums behalf or to provide services available at AdForums websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using AdForums websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. AdForum will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, AdForum discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when AdForum believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AdForum, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an AdForum website and have supplied your email address, AdForum may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with AdForum and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. AdForum takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitors computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AdForum uses cookies to help AdForum identify and track visitors, their usage of AdForum website, and their website access preferences. AdForum visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using AdForums websites, with the drawback that certain features of AdForums websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Although most changes are likely to be minor, AdForum may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in AdForums sole discretion. AdForum encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

| 

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
  
---  
  
At AdForum.com, the privacy of our users is one of our top concerns. The following statement discloses our privacy policies for AdForum.com, a service provided by MayDream. Maydream and AdForum.com are herein also referred to as "us" and "this site."  
  
**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY**

Maydream provides a business-to-business service. We only collect personal information from users when it is related to their professional activity. We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

### 1\. Registration

To access certain areas of the AdForum.com website (especially creative work), you must first complete a registration form to become either member (and access to Agency Preview’s agency portfolio’s for free) or subscriber (and get a full access to AdFolio for a fee). During registration, you may be required to provide professional contact information, such as name, email address and company type, to provide mailing address and payment information, and to choose a password. Your email is your login. We send all new registered members and subscribers a welcoming email to verify their password and username. When an email address is not working, the associated password might be deactivated by Maydream.

### 2\. Subscription to the Newsletter

Should a user wish to receive our newsletter, we require them to provide professional contact information, such as name, company type and email address. Our newsletters are usually distributed via email.

### 3\. Registration of a company in our database

Agencies, productions companies and other businesses may add themselves to AdForum.com directories. During the online process that allows them to do so, the personal information of the user who inputs the data is requested: name, email and phone number. An AdForum.com Information Center member may use this information to contact this person for verification purposes.  
If the company decides to buy an upgraded listing in our directory, see also buyer information collection below.

### 4\. Buyer information collection

When buying a service on the site, users are asked for contact, billing and shipping information. These data may be used to process the order, to get the payment through the credit card company, to personalize the product(s) and/or the service(s) according to the order, and to ship the item(s) related to the ordered service, like questionnaires. If there is a problem with the order, a Maydream Representative may contact the user by email, phone, fax or mail. A confirmation email is sent for each online purchase.

### 5\. Request for information

When requesting information from AdForum.com (sales brochure, price list, press kit, service demo by phone, etc.), users must first complete a registration form. During registration, a user may be required to provide professional contact information, such as name, company, company address, phone number, email address, and company type. This information is used to deliver the information the user has requested.

### 6\. Surveys and Contests

From time to time, we request information from AdForum.com users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. Information requested may include contact information and business information (name, company, occupation, responsibilities, email and shipping address). This information is mainly used to better understand our audience and to send prizes to the winners when needed. Should the results of a contest or a survey be published, no personal information will be divulged.

### 7\. Prospect information collection

To use our “Refer/Send to a friend” services, users are requested to provide names and email addresses that may be used later as prospect information. For these “Refer/Send to a friend” services, AdForum.com sends an email to a prospect (or prospects) on behalf of the user containing links to the information the user has selected on the AdForum.com website. Each of these emails provides the prospect with the opportunity to opt-out of further communication from AdForum.com. 

### 1\. AdForum.com's newsletters and e-alerts

AdForum subscribes for free the users of its website who submit their email address for any of the purposes listed above to its newsletters and e-alerts. These publications are aimed at professionals of the marketing and advertising industry. Any subscriber who doesn’t want to receive these newsletters or email alerts anymore can easily unsubscribe, as detailed in “Opt-out” below.

### 2\. General communication from Maydream

Users and prospects will occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals from Maydream, regarding AdForum.com or another site published by Maydream. No other company but Maydream will ever access the user and prospect personal information. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see our opt-out policy below.

### 3\. Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their personal information used for marketing purposes not directly related to out site.   
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletters, e-alerts or promotional materials may opt-out by:   
\- Removing their email address from our database at: click here   
\- Replying to the email message with the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line   
\- Sending a letter to MayDream, 6W 18th Street, 8th Floor, NY, USA   
When the user makes an “unsubscribe” request we commit to remove the email address from our mailing lists as soon as possible, and usually before the next mailing.

### 4\. Sharing of information

 a - Agency Preview and Production Preview   
The information collected from companies listed in Agency Preview and Production Preview is shared with Maydream’s partners when the service is locally co-branded under a partnership. No individual or personal information is ever shared. Maydream asks its partners to ensure that they reflect the same attention and commitment to privacy as AdForum.com, but doesn’t guarantee it and cannot be hold responsible for their actions.   
 b - E-store   
The information collected during the purchase of books and publications offered in partnership with third parties in our e-store is shared with these partners to allow them to fulfill their obligations and send the products that have been bought through our site. No credit card information is ever shared. Maydream asks its partners to ensure that they reflect the same attention and commitment to privacy as AdForum.com, but doesn’t guarantee it and cannot be hold responsible for their actions.   
 c - Other information   
Maydream is the sole owner of information collected on the AdForum.com website for other purpose than detailed in 4a and 4b. We will not sell, disclose, or rent this information to others except if required to through a legal proceeding or law.   
We may share aggregated information with our partners and advertisers. However, this information is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Maydream carefully review the privacy policies of partners, affiliates and subsidiaries to ensure that they reflect the same attention and commitment to privacy as AdForum.com   
Maydream may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

### 5\. Outside data

From time to time, for marketing purposes, Maydream may combine information disclosed by a user on the AdForum.com site with information about that user obtained from other sources.

### 6\. Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are only linked to member's personally identifiable information.

### 7\. Cookies

AdForum.com website may uses cookies and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.  
OpenX, our digital advertising service, also uses cookies to collect information from our users. Real Media has absolutely no access to any personal information from the users.

### 8\. Correcting / Updating personnal information

We provide a way to correct or update user personal data from our records should information change. For a user who no longer desires to be on our mailing list, see our opt-out process.  
A delay of 3 days applies to corrections and updates of personal information as Maydream attempts to verify the identity of a user requesting such changes to their information before they are made.  
To correct or update personal information, send an email to our Customer Support Department or send a letter to MayDream, Information Center, 6W 18th Street, 8th Floor, NY, USA.

### 9\. Accessing your information

To review your personal or business information held by Maydream, please address us an email to this effect or write to MayDream, 6W 18th Street, 8th Floor, NY, USA. We will ensure you are who you claim before we disclose any information.

### 1\. Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings..

### 2\. Links

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that Maydream is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

### 3\. Notification of changes

This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 12, 2003. When we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a message on our homepage to that effect with a link to the revised Policy. In this way, users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances we may disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of email and users will be given a choice as to whether or not Maydream may use their information in this different manner.

If you have general inquiries regarding the privacy or security practices of Maydream, please contact us by email.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
